{
  "LANGHINDI": 18,
  "qu1": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following clustering algorithm is suitable for categorical data?</p>",
      "OPT1": "<p>\r\n\tk-Means</p>",
      "OPT2": "<p>\r\n\tk-Medoids</p>",
      "OPT3": "<p>\r\n\tk-Median</p>",
      "OPT4": "<p>\r\n\tk-Mode</p>",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu2": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhat is the function of the hidden layers in a multilayer perceptron (MLP)?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Hidden layers perform feature extraction and transformation",
      "OPT2": "Hidden layers provide direct access to the input data",
      "OPT3": "Hidden layers perform the final classification or regression task",
      "OPT4": "Hidden layers are not necessary in an MLP",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu3": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following options corresponds to cluster analysis?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Simple segmentation",
      "OPT2": "Labeled classification",
      "OPT3": "Grouping similar objects",
      "OPT4": "Query result grouping",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu4": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhat is the time complexity of naive agglomerative hierarchical clustering using priority queue data structures?</p>",
      "OPT1": "\u039f(n)",
      "OPT2": "<p>\r\n\t\u039f(n<sup>2</sup> log n)</p>",
      "OPT3": "<p>\r\n\t\u039f(n<sup>2</sup>)</p>",
      "OPT4": "<p>\r\n\t\u039f(n<sup>3</sup>)</p>",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu5": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following activation function is commonly used in feed-forward neural networks for classification tasks?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Linear activation function",
      "OPT2": "Sigmoid activation function",
      "OPT3": "ReLU (Rectified Linear Unit) activation function",
      "OPT4": "Softmax activation function",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "VZe7U2dj9zYleEGzXPWVbg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "VZe7U2dj9zYleEGzXPWVbg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu6": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following statements is/are correct?<br />\r\n\t<em>S</em><sub>1</sub> : K-means clustering reduces the variance with in clusters.<br />\r\n\t<em>S</em><sub>2</sub> : Mean-shift clustering identify the modes in the density distribution of data points and assign them to clusters.</p>",
      "OPT1": "<p>\r\n\tOnly <em>S</em><sub>1</sub></p>",
      "OPT2": "<p>\r\n\tOnly <em>S</em><sub>2</sub></p>",
      "OPT3": "<p>\r\n\tBoth <em>S</em><sub>1</sub> and <em>S</em><sub>2</sub></p>",
      "OPT4": "None of these",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu7": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following sequence of implementation of Agglomerative Hierarchical Clustering (AHC)?<br />\r\n\t<strong>I.</strong> Preprocessing the data.<br />\r\n\t<strong>II.</strong> Analyzing the dendrogram to determine the optimal number of clusters.<br />\r\n\t<strong>III.</strong> Creating visual representations of the clusters.<br />\r\n\t<strong>IV.</strong> Training the hierarchical clustering algorithm.</p>",
      "OPT1": "I, II, III, IV",
      "OPT2": "II, IV, III, I",
      "OPT3": "I, II, IV, III",
      "OPT4": "IV, III, II, I",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu8": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tGiven the distance matrix below, which pair of points will be merged first in single linkage clustering?</p>\r\n<p>\r\n\t<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAATMAAACBCAYAAACsLV2UAAAb/0lEQVR4Xu1dfVCWVdr/qe2Xq+X08QZqu01OQDO1pZCuozMqrmYTJguV74powTj4hooxQKKwWSCgMCAKlbkQH35MNaCFhisD4k40pdDoWBM4675tjZFj46g51rQu73vu+7lveB54jHPzXOe+n3Pv8U889znX+Z3r+p3P5/qN+j/2D+qfQkAhoBCQHIFRiswkH0FlvkJAIaAjoMhMOYJCQCHgCgSGJbNRo0a5oqOqEwqB/3QE3H6ixEVmMoOgkbGy39kwVmOg8LcDAUVmdqAcQBuyE4F+lqEmlAA8IPBPZcefFwFFZrxIOVTODY4oex+U/Q45v8VmFZlZBMzu4rIHklqZ2e0xQ9tzgw/xoKjIjAclB8u4wRFl74Oy38EAsNC0IjMLYDlRVPZAUiszJ7zGt003+BAPiorMeFBysIwbHFH2Pij7HQwAC00rMuMBq++faFwVg/hqIKnhEHbHheLCid3YEPsmQvYcwdboO3lqGVEZkkBy0H6aldmPON+YjkfjK7UBwMndcQi90IHyDatRHFKO7q3RuHVE6PJ9JPsYkNjPB5WjpRSZDQt/H66278WBkMcw88M1CH9rET7/Swia236D5IXAOYRhaujPh61lpAUCd0Rn7Schs6sdqD5wG56aeQJPhx/B0s9fwR3NpxGePBvfnxuNh6eGYvRIAeb4TvYxCNx+DpCCoIgiMwuD0He2Go+Hvwpkb0Z1fgwmiYwgwy5KR3TCfhIyM8eorxvVj8egCsuQVZ2DJZPETSLebiH7GFDabyFcbC+qyMwK5De6UBKxFGe2HUNt3D1WvhxxWVJHdMB+UjLDNXSVLEbUmbX4upZtNUeMqrUPZR8DUvutQWdraUVmVuC+dgIli5NxZu37vmTW14uupkN4e/tpzNi3HXGht1ip9SfLkjqiX/uv4mxjEVLiC9HO6GFuVgV25cYibBzdspOuD5cZmS1nZJY0iMx+RK9+hrkGdb30faCznw31zXzI8IK+3hbkLHsXUYR+RGo/mWfTV6TIjBtTFkhledjReRQtk70OnXvfR8neHzBv3g/YEfU3LPm6IkjJ7Cb2s61b7eYe/GHzEnaorgXS/6Ar8RCakyLIzqFogqkP17rewEs7/or9LQ9gT3c+om81CFfbfq5qwL35mZjbdwirHt2JB5qakBE5jnt0f6ogjf1aCzcZg/5ttHnRNAsNhH5EZz8JnMIqUWQ2HLTXzqK95xe4/8o7qLz8R6SiGJN3hqNzXzRO7/wMs/OXIUyLqd5GrJx4NPjIjNd+HQfPNm4pStCdEQmq9WVgwcRWju3n8Ov7v8WuyutISf03Nk6uxkOdlYg5vR8fz16PlSEfoexACNJWhuE6I7y8vz2E9WmzEEq0uAzMfg1WHh9iFzVtr6Hq8hicij9F6kcB2z9cjATJ/ysyG2YgPIfmZQip2o/KpAcx9nwjm/nj0bygGBXrEhAbadykBSmZcduv4aAfsGfjUsGbbFUzgcxFAwom3aZo5IQUoq0yERFjv/I8k2mehuKKdUiIjfSQllEu+WgvELoCpQeLkDad5pYzIPs103h8iG0/ywp68YxO1rSTYqD2kzmC4IoUmVEBHKRkxt897S1XLv58ORHljLRpNmie1m0Npr7zaMtJwvyupehpTvKsmgP8J97+H3C2ugAfzN6IpPHvk6/wxdsfIMBEnysyIwIyaLeZXP3znEflnZ6NXGIis53MoG3XchBRG4UuohtP4WRwtQ0vRszHNraoHPg3F8WdNOd+wu3n8jHxhRSZEWHs2UqcQArhwa09RMCIrHsv8vaFYP3mBWTnTN6wig6mvrO1WFUzEfn5zP7rn6I6tRCX1lWSbZVF2+/jggJW+LbaTxRPI6lGkdlIUPP55gZblK3BxPhdxl+nYEUD3Ts00Y7oeQqwEoXtXsuCKcXo7M5AJNENgOg+DD4vK67dhNULwsi2ysLt1z1nsB+plZnV0FRkZhUxm8vbE0hiOyV7H5T9Yv2DqnZFZlRICqpH9kCyZ6ssCHyjWtnHQHb7eUdXkRkvUg6Vc4Mjyt4HZb9Dzm+xWUVmFgGzu7jsgaRWZnZ7zND23OBDPChykRlPRaqMQkAhENwIyCy5yIMsF5nJDILss5Ls9quVGU8Yii3jBh/iQUiRGQ9KDpZxgyPK3gdlv4MBYKFpRWYWwHKiqOyBpFZmTniNb5tu8CEeFBWZ8aDkYBk3OKLsfVD2OxgAFppWZGYBrIGiLC1NSxW2rExnyQDZX1mWBupX52Zb4gPJSM6YdTtKCF/9e8MqpA8srU7L61uwMrMO+m8X5mahpmQ9Es0sJiMaV/8fCbHfuykjuWfDh9cw7bEnsCia7tcLblgZ8w6lIjNepPrLGUpBa75HflsZksK+82RpKPwZ+2HwHrLfA9pDZtoPzMuxOCod7cQ/YRJLZlqWiVRsuZKEIpa37G49qST7SVZPHBpOliKOWBtAHJkx/M8eRN7awwjJyydLWTTYpcXZbzl4hH6gyMwqvGZ+rUf2DEicGVkP6hNbyWXPhDqilsI5tRJnvmxB3VfppL/HFEtmLKdZcjUmlOUa2WY1clvB1JoukmWaEGu/p/Y+PTdeNcuKSz8J2mG/1dARXd4eMnNQt5GaDDzZMXKAqraB1NJmYsBz9IRAbf+AQ2n59Dfj2LzncN+OeMR3rJaIzAaHhUFm9TPR2ZSGSEL9AmHbNCMm1twpie6naCYiqN8GMnNWt5GaDG50lSAi6nXM8smMwVYKK+cJIQRq+02f0dPmvPcAyjNCcVSQ7bZtlbvrkZr2BVbWZCNagIapiDEwZf8erNqAycdfRnrdpwyuhciqycP6xOmkqZhE2E/APeRV2EBmAzY7odtIPZCuIDNtVfA80//MzWPnSxeEEbFoMvP4UzKOmg0JugSg9iHA3BZ/4KWGxaQC9PPLvZjeegRbo+8kC3Z6+8lMI63IVjKDA7qN1AMpP5lpmVg3Y9kXy/CersAkblUpmsy8pknPQXrKGmxrn42qnjp2MfNLskCh9iFTOCYq8y5fW/XEjPFoyaI9e6W3nwxa0orsJbNhNANJe2ZURj2QHjIrxRR/Z2YhFeTitNT2+yQy9AP4lOJOUmUmYWdOQ2wXdwlAPgammHFmuK+knCKzgCjARjL7Cc1AWUR0Naj93Vzqf1uOU/lelwIBDcvAx/SBNNgwCVdmDO+NRcCGgmjc2t8dQ+388JPklwD0Y2DoFMw/ikSvLaWp4jS54RB2x/02yHRLiRxaYDXiyWw4zcDUCXhvvwwiuuYoGKramf9Cdms18qPHs2cBLyA651eokOqNk9Ef8yb2zLNo9RbWJXQ6cjLQbV6O44vK9XdmoaMNRfNln2DOIfb2L2KA4ii6QW6/ZpS+S4lFJlLQuo9dXIw/y7QL/oTkL5MkIGMKVOnrEE5mXJqBWr8ECDkI2+KwleSJ8g2ITfe8Pg9dUYraTclYEEYbRMLs1/3IWJHVnfPxKjm2mYy82gqxbP5mtOvWP4gVxS9jXUIMIiW5zdSs7us9gfrtuXh2m3aFofWhBJtWL0CYDE9L6Lko4BqFkxm3hTKRGXenAi8oZFUQuFmWapC9D8p+S8PtWGFFZo5Bz9ew7IEkdnXJh2GgpWQfA9nt5x0/RWa8SDlUzg2OKHsflP0OOb/FZoOGzOQV0bWIuMXisgeSWplZHHABxd3gQzywBAGZyS2iywNyIGXc4Iiy90HZH4gH2/dtEJCZ2M4qRxSLL0/tagx4UBJXRnb8eZFRZMaLlEPl3OCIsvdB2e+Q81tsVpGZRcDsLi57IKkzM7s9Zmh7bvAhHhS5yIynIlVGIaAQCG4EZJaM5EGWi8xkBkH2WUl2+9XKjCcMxZZxgw/xIKTIjAclB8u4wRFl74Oy38EAsNC0IjMLYDlRVPZAUiszJ7zGt003+BAPiorMeFBysIwbHFH2Pij7HQwAC00rMrMAlhNFZQ8ktTJzwmvUyswv6rIHk3D7r3WjMS8NWXcVkGdoFUoEg0R0ZUtj5Mn4mwnfBEaAHCmMvkXbi4swf1uXn5gLxdzig2jKmI5xRDwoPAaI7Ay0GrUyCwhBM1HjYSFBJIzMTJmzGxloq0xE2HetHhFdlipQFqk2jcymvj0NHVu9s80GNJg3/ZieDLSsuDk4/WSRr1aBlrF4WiNmHKcVMqa3XwzOgdZqD5m5SDdzAHBNDbwCqTs+xpd1+/CVgNz5osjMVMl6pD9ls/80zoE6l/m9iGDSyOz3x+bho4xI3EJl6E3qobefkVnZblxJTjNEjLWGtYnxOWy8vXBAj5WoX/T2ExlGXI0NZOYu3cx+/HU18I8wb9NE7Ah/Gh3SkJkp/MF0jL1UjEzZtnMC+iEimOQms6FRrKubz+lEwif5XgRHE+0i8KexjLYWG8jMay2j6xwyvcbszajOj8Gk0bSd8VebmIHUCOElvPdwNjImtunyYPKQmSH8cRNlIBH9EDEG+jZzRy8Wfrkfpe168nKmQbkVJeuXkqfOFmG/r69qZ2gJ2DvjDVIhE5ErY/GRa70FW8nMDbqZGsTaLPp8HtPQfTUOky54tA5FkICYbaZbyKwMsW//FqW5sSxn/jWcbSxCSnwh2hdWoac5CWGEE6VYMtOOK5j4bwZQ0pSGSOL8/2J8yDrR2PGFvWTmAt1MQJtFc/BF8nbP4a2hdajI7ObuKpYMzHbNG8L7JBAB9sLKUJrqSGkQsipTZOaFNZ0j3kw3k81M/WrUbLswNxsNuzYgjkjpiM5+Dyjm2ZKmpzP031wUdzYhI5LqUh2gtv9matqefhUgpOEYauPuIZ1I6fvgzzxzxTlIJZygJ+Ls/xHnG9Px6M4paBK0KlNkRklmw+lm5scB9a/h0z+kIi70ItpykjC/aynZVkGcIxogSbcy83dzaf7t78j3uhQg4AG9CvIxuNqOkqqxWP2C91ssY2V26nky3xF+5iRQPNp77Mjxp3IM4nqEbzO5dTONjumPIZcCb3VnIJLgzl30QJortTNZregW8OZJiP03EaDNueVlnNzNzgEJz5uEkJn+1Ie9iUsoYyLMkzCa6Zh21W9HRs1Y5GqCusTamULGQH+KsRxRpb8TJr4snIyJySjQ6oSTmTUDtVvCZKRcSiN7AS3GEVmvjBVZnU8HZdhmGtvl3g6Ub1iN9LpP2R/ECdAKITOwo4nueqRGP4s67SITC5FV9SKSn5lLLqArzH7t0D8qHT2CJkG1MvPDPMLIwE9b+i3hn7/D+vJERBDd6thpvzXi5istu/1iyIAPO6pSso+B7PbzjmPwrMzY1qcsrweP5yaQEZkKJF43EFtO9mBS9ov1D6rag4PMrn2K6rwjuHf9OknOO6jgH74e2QNJTSjDj7HoEm7wIR6MnCezvvOeG8xC78cOdGdPsg+k7PYrMuMJQ7Fl3OBDPAg5T2Y8VgZQRvaBlN1+RWYBOC/Rp27wIR4oFJnxoORgGTc4oux9UPY7GAAWmlZkZgEsJ4rKHkhqZeaE1/i26QYf4kFRkRkPSg6WcYMjyt4HZb+DAWChaS4ys1CfKqoQUAgEKQIy69/yQMpFZjKDoGZVHjcQW0aNgVh8h6tddvyH65/5/4rMeJFyqJwbHFH2Pij7HXJ+i80qMrMImN3FZQ8kdQFgt8cMbc8NPsSDoiIzHpQcLOMGR5S9D8p+BwPAQtOKzCyA1V90kOYkSz6PmpL1SIwMBXH2HPpcYFonbnShJCIKmUNFJ9FJlHrJG1YxZHAVZ1uqsGVluidzRugKFNduwuoFYWR6k/1nMaNGgf7cWEtK2oLXt2Qg08xcUvo6itJmIZTYicTgP5LAEfuNIjPL+GppilKx5UqS7nh3X2jxaE72xKHhJK3eobAtmkZmUxswrYNeCcgfnPTBZGRoXfM98tvKWPry74yfxP2MZfrdwzL9TrA8qj/1Ab39rDU9MWMavsk0COw6+31y6lp0LKkhT58txH5ShGkqU2RmGcev0JhcjQlluYYkmCnddpE8ZbZQMvv9Mcz7iCYB5nAQkgeTnjc/GjmP7BlIiKmTw3zUJ9InySS3X18ca4rsf8e2rytYhmUtC6mR7Xc5sKebdpIRYf9wY+7E/9tEZsZMGl8JJDXo2UxDL3iSAxaHlAvJ0Cp2i+A9VAaZ1c+URg1c32ZKTGae7L45TPizbUAw1yC45HPp5FtlEWQwOAPzONAnJrUvBpygrqFt2kNmVztQfeA2PDXzBJ4OP4Kln7+CO5pPIzx5Nr4/NxoPT6U/a7JnII2Mp2lfYGUNfbpmoSuzqaW4uPBbbCs1spVIdO7nWdW8jlk+4itsxbxyHuI7VktBZkyvsD9bTOiKYuyYMwZfjJmFhMTp6sxshNxoD5mZxumzZwyqsAxZ1TlYMunnIzSb/zMRs6rW+hCVJkFkIMR+bWUW24D7SjUVrHFe6lizyWXaRBCyK8hM8yEtdXlOPb6Z8L+eSUUmH+IPQdtK2ktmMOTAzqzF17Vsq2lDN4WQgY/d3lJ59GQg3n6dmtl5dA4i5tfgIe+tG9H4UPfBDWSmpYhfNacNTxz3XBr19Z5A/fZcPLuN/hKDGn8ityCvxmYyMxRpziT5kJk+Q5niGkGum+l/BMRdAtjliB6CKMUUachskK3mmVlIBflEST8Gnkl98cVc3/NiQdJz9PaT8xBJhTaSmSZD/wZe2vFX7G95wOvGRiOCTai5Nx35c2/g4KoYZD1Qg+6MSBAozdG/02IOt7EI2FAQjVv7h8BYcR5+kvwSgN4Rmb5kyQHctjoZkf2iMbLpZvq5uRREBCK2yTBk5hZfTPdDZlnsOvMItkbfSRLgYuwnM420IhvIjD1ubD+HX9//LXZVXkdK6r+xcXI1HuqsRMzp/fh4diLuOfwBJqctRdh1TdTkE8xan4TpRNqH5GSgrwCW4/iicuOB44/oPbEbG5Z9gjmH2JuniAGKoxgpcvuh3SxnIanzCdTkL2CHzcz+rrewPeMtjMnd5dGhpDDcqw76Phgr/Mx/Ibu1mtk8nk2ILyA651eokOWtn65d+gouri1BblwExl3rRmNeGtZ8swxtlXTqZIrMKB3RfBMUUugZpLHs1omtvuKbp6G4Yh0SYiNZQJnbtHdYy0zDkfAlNH0gseBvK8Sy+ZvRruOkaU6+jHUJMYgkImBvLqG3n9WuCcik/gnJ+svzUHbunI/c5KcQHUZLxGY/hPSBCf+eKN+A2PQ6eH4AUIraTclYIKAPQuzXtD99fgEgTvtTjP3EMx5BdTaszKxYaRLFZ0jsqWMvu39p5WO/ZWUfSNntd8PKQPYxkN1+XhIIMjJjZutnH29jRpf5Mpq3K/7LyT6QstuvyCww/6X42g0+xIOD82SmbUNXNeDe/EymmfkDuquzkHYpCQ0Z00l+MCz7QMpuvyIznjAUW8YNPsSDkPNkpv+MYwX7NYBxXlZcgk2rFyCs/6aNpxs3LyP7QMpuvyKzwPyX4ms3+BAPDkFAZjxmjryM7AMpu/2KzEbuu1RfusGHeLBQZMaDkoNl3OCIsvdB2e9gAFhoWpGZBbCcKCp7IKmVmRNe49umG3yIB0VFZjwoOVjGDY4oex+U/Q4GgIWmucjMQn2qqEJAIRCkCNCn/g6ujnKRmcwgqFnVeYdTY+DsGMiOPy96isx4kXKonBscUfY+KPsdcn6LzSoyswiY3cVlDyR1AWC3xwxtzw0+xIOiIjMelBws4wZHlL0Pyn4HA8BC04rMLIDlr2hfbxeamg/hw0sReOzJx8kzT9AHEstn9uIizN/W5ac7LING8UE0Ef2UzGyAvg9azUN1M0sPFiFtOr2ehBj7WRcG6a+KyvwhzP4AY4f6c0VmI0aUBVNjEda+Owl5RavI8q8NNofeEbVEkjk4/WSRb1YS7Qf+0xoxw0jjPGJY/HxI3wdTlu08MnUCuxvXu+uRGnMSS6Swn4HU9089FdaaGxl6aqyw71o9+qvIlCDBJ6V30NWlyGxEWBrSeTunoKkpzStj64gq+8mP6ImAkVnZblxJTjN0P7XmtWSHz2Hj7YUD0m2EXRHSB5Z2OspHS8Kz4lyObeTShfT2m4I4r+KRVjOrrJnt9ygS+/9GMwgi7KexjLYWe8jMmIXiqzXZzENMsTkUF7TsrLFvIoQ4RbD4lQ1zRE2M4tEC3CnYdq0vdjiiR1yjEwmf0IrPittmGskJcsYz6Uwju6+eBDQblwrelEDR3EyuwKQ/vfL2mYpf54o7ydLG2+VDtLQ0stpsIDM247TvxYGQxzDzwzUIf2sRPv9LCJrbfoPkhcA5hGGqgAyt4gNpIqrevA/Hn0tDnZbqVFqZMG1Fk4C9M95gk8xvyVNmiwqmvt4Wz7as/Q6W6TcLc/Atxsz7byRGynBmZmhGZIajoV/RnCHV24iVE+PRochsRGxmA5kN2OWZeV4FsjejOj8Gk6iTzdtxXmOqAB19CFkN5Z787YZARVTp79DaTbu6Ebsy00RmyrE4AygRuF0W0weP9kLOrn9gwj/2o7Rdm0+2omT9UvL05fT2KzIbEVsN85GtZAZNfDZiKc5sO4bauHtE9GdIneSOqPchCplTqtDTnIQwnZBvsEl1DSbGdyJLpvMOQ5ylI6VB2KpMzMrMc2Y553A0ju+OY5OiKcryIjsxk+EAXZGZiOC3l8x0RZpknFn7vl8y82wd3kXUvu2IC6UQmhNw5mSS2awGL31GGclM4ksMfQxScPENb0k2cXJ55BOiKYadeZefM7MChDTQTvb09ougosDrtJHM2I1ZWR52dB5Fy+TyoTdO/ZcEs3zPEQLsI/1AGu+06hd6bSnNA+n/QgOx1Bm9/QagAnUmhV/C6JPiC7iY+66XvqT5XIPJTgb9Vt/fzaVMZBxgUAr6XDyZsYeB7T2/wP1X3kHl5T8iFcWYvDMcnfuicXrnZ5idv4xt1bSBfA1Vl8fgVPwpLPE+FA2w4/RkYJwzRRWzs79a7Mufj/Fn2Run6Gx8mS7Lg1NDd1LAGZ+/4RI2BhkXsXbXBsSFjWPvTw8iL6UA3yTWoDLpQRL9CHGXSKxmnZBj2aY4Ba37shE9/qwu/5dzy8s4qW+dA3R8r8/p8aezjbIm4WTmOfQvQ0jVft3JxurPGuLRvKAYFesSEKvdPrGBLSvoxTO6QPDRICczDX6vM5p2dpUZugLFtZuwekEYaRCJOW8yyTgdPVmt5G+y7CEzrZVBvwBgt8lVucl4JlqGMfCg1NfbgfINq5Gu65dq+qu0+hdCyZiShYjqEk5mw9upbdEK8MHsjUga/z67mpaBzIbvFVUJN8yqsvdB2U/lzWLrcZ7M9LOb+dimvdXq/zcXxZ1N7PHjuIB7rxwxYAgDrkCNQcAQBlSB7Pjzdt55MvO2VH80qFZm3pC4wRFl74Oyn5dOnC0XJGRmPm3YZaChVmZuOu9QZOBwkI8aBZmzRfOiFyRkxmuu9XIqkKxjRv2FGgNqRK3VJzv+vL1VZMaLlEPl3OCIsvdB2e+Q81tsVpGZRcDsLi57IGl4yd4HZb/dXj+y9rjIbGRVq68UAgqBYELA7edmw5JZMA2GskUhoBBQCNwMAUVmyjcUAgoBVyCgyMwVw6g6oRBQCCgyUz6gEFAIuAIBRWauGEbVCYWAQuD/Adi2CrmFam/TAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" /></p>",
      "OPT1": "<p>\r\n\t<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAD8AAAAhCAYAAABug3M0AAADpElEQVRoQ+2Ze0hUaRjGfy4RsWvhYm2DQQVLSQgRk4ILUUMUXaDd0W6YSbMpsqylTUEGOkZppdPF2dSKGGOibaMJbWyXNnaNhvCPKbcpumISQbvUdLdJKMrOdDxzNK2xZc45hTDn/H3O873P9zzf+z7fTFxIfIjRJ04nrysfezug2z72NA8z1pXXlY/BHdBtH4Oi6w1Pt32P7YXAaTZvukd23XImfDHIDoPQxsECD+M2WjEZhmpS3DvlO1txLN4FW/ayxpigCbi2IAKd/jqWlkD5sQKM8erVkcl34K/OxfJ4NS0VJkZoW7V2aMIdmgpy2D9xB0etacSrRJbIC+0uFs7+nRmN9YNU9d6DSdC7iWk/BylvruKHJHX2F8m/CLW78phn/xanbyOmEWE7CXc9rJpl5S/M7OxeyPCEf2ptrNyXxO4+7yndfMX4QS+29AKurm+kwZKMGvOL5P8NNeV9zzrKaHGaMUhsHnHWdZbRmZPw5WTjyXBRk3gO78QMZr24D5NTMKhZVQ1+d+PLyKR81JY+9SqTIC70+kLIkbaQ2qnVEcBeIrni8BuWF1ZRtmCsqp3+sEQl+P8hiXUhB3erFeMQZcTDt7qPkocufzXpmbex+XaJ1lex0gA1Ro//2cjL4yWznfxPQl4Jvpbke878w0L+PG7pH27E2V9TcYCLJ64zZk8D5aaRvfoJAT8nTzWytyWV+t5eEaUFB8LvbKOpcj3rfr0sAk4my2Gn2JwsjzaZfL8eFeW68usRuj10trdy86tvCDrdPMtbDGXZ7E9xUD//FvvOTyE/4QzuN6lMFw6z5OTMfr1CCLTyW20lRxI3DDCLRbU/ij+V0vRLbLv2HSVmAw+828m13GDJ305WTBiGOOu07PbinJfGWjWJkrrx4SZnH47teBUrkodx11PM3DU+0ouK+SlrPkYpXnYR8Kxl2h99ycsNzD4qPB4jzuGed/4PX5any48jrRTq3WIG+VLrOd/9p4WShBeBvDSG8jn34yFqzdpMBimAFT7HJkXaJ3hLs9ieuFW7hCftcdTZ/n3yr0SHbKaiIwu7JUV19AwnLTHOFtXQscomOjBeyvY5e76m0rGMZO2yfdhi0d3qItleWeOJ/JXoxt11XJmzWiQu3jY+6a0u6rrls9uySHXS+nDpIG2uX3CPz6XElKRxsHq3msIfM+Rx0/xURlrATs1ywCsCUod30tZnVxKKGvBZjWgZsxSSj9omg/IDnfyglOUzFPUWGntFvFrYq9QAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" /></p>",
      "OPT2": "<p>\r\n\t<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAEAAAAAZCAYAAACB6CjhAAAEMElEQVRYR+2Yf0yUdRzHX7rWWhKzXdbt3MytgJnpGOo6stWtdIUr4WCghBe3QLM4fsmSGhwqJwIa3AkcKt21M7MtDDxirSwqYppXV2QUFd2yrZVepkUnM+b06rkf4EFH8+4eik2ev55ne57v9/N5fz6f9/v9fWb8JVxcw9eMaQCmO2B6BMZwgNv5HpXbTpNlXEfMzClGDu4B9udZuX1LMQrp9aIEN5YDhuwY0uuhag9FCbNF2UDcRdwM9RpZUwa6Q3kkREVeoQAABunV56A+l8/R7QqixY1cvNXcP9KRp6Il9gVeK15GVIQrjwLgdlhIW9nJA+3mKVr9kUzduLq3cd8zLnRdtSTLIhsFPwDDOCy5JO28A5NtC4poX2u5T1nRrCjmHVKo82wm/Y1Pm7Q8uVdGQ8B74RXhIqespTxSZIUkPW8bU5CeOY6xfBMvSqv/vQtd3WjleXy1uZ02dRyRDIIfgJ/oyF1NCRUcNQmBeDM6S4+lh9tSF2BTZWFVWmiUfEx3rJIVf/4CixcijWRn13H2d0SjlNvJXtlFyhEtkiN9xKiXM3xyJovipRMn5iFDZSq6OVUB8YZXBh8Al3oxLEujaYk+yIL+7jh4mXUFtVQ8Ni8ixP8RpjeZTF5FSf6eUh69qpb2F+wzFa32YhKuCy95z1dXAQACPnrkqT+gtdULYxDBbkHjHBLIN4OM/g0hVPM/BcAvPakONkwKAD71yehX/Y8A4Ef01wLeOqwea4AEb9C4/SU+f+Nr5ja3oVPc4qvj0AAdNZspeaVPeFhMpmEnpSlxIcqSB1wzVc3v8+ZHsWOI1e30EeLuLicseIK6hhKSY0bEORhnhTcGE6iAkJ/DznezbsVlauWP3HSoyKJloQHzqu/Z+8kSyuUnqO5PpCxFypnuXeSovyHjXRPZgn109r6OsawTyYSGyoWj5ySz7jyHed8Fcp66zNZ7D3BXu56kvlbsy9dzz7FqDs4voOL+S3TmrUEXa8RWnIB3AMVXgRHJ0yPxVjnKL4s3oT1cS3bcDX7JsiEvLGVj5ioSAq2ol0TLwdxKUfzPXoauk1V5pU0WTCn8LF4353kOGR4n7kahokKSJR/ejWbH06xdPY9vmz5griadmAtCB9acIFGTzVLvnpPiAzywhu8EvSaq4DxawZ7Gn36ZtOQvUEdsUvzqs/WYEJuUBzfVU6lJFKT3LN3lmeyS7BDXCfrmOoyzgMeaFjYyqNEK7T945T5OLDN9EefoiLWQdt6MqvlmajydI+5ZwEcioZ0Gha5pMPLlw/nCmIiVcBAy8858O0u7NjKo65zE02BIROpiwLKb1vk5lClk4puj0WPvsLBPOc/9ruKACIef8SmG+UtspC1NDASsOLuw7QpThwTm+JfHzX9hJc+uf4gYEVpeJAAiym5KfRxmB0ypHCIKZhqAa/23+N+4tjLUV/I9ewAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" /></p>",
      "OPT3": "<p>\r\n\t<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAEAAAAAmCAYAAAB0xJ2ZAAADu0lEQVRoQ+2Zf0iUdxzHX40YsbkoXNutoA02kyHIOBWMte0IB02oqWVxqWXNiXTL0pgXlGemDXVLjzSN0Lj9OCNHdrnRRjgm4Ui7uhFF1I4xGKNdVKsOaRH21HN3z7U7O3XPD+Wg5/n7+7w/n+f9+fH+fL7PjIfiw1P8zNAJiJEBgu8ndtf+TcH+QpKeibP0EK7wpcXFqzUVmAzPqnbuyQwYcWPPb4Y9HWw1zlFtQHsAgRHPftbsgLpvLRgT1EVoDAG38bR8RPHNzQzWm5itvffaIAp/ctxSxMFFX3CkIoMEFahRBAheByvf/473erviNPrhLxXwD9SyZJOfuv5GPpyvvBQiCLiH11HCB02v0zlUg2l2KLWEqy4+yargJDnsDRgz/MPZtmo2HpjPvohzSoOgGN8/QHWmhYtVvRwtTkZpIUQQ8BfHS1awDRuDnTkYgl90g1OOU7yc9yZDRQW4ch20Jg4zsCiXrH+vQWoKBqWW1eIHmmFuHnXz9kT4Kz8M/xEw6sGesZK2tJYYgFJ2OB9QWN6IbflCxYzHdlEJvhSwc0X0uCswzpT/8YE3/icBMOppITPvD6qHmsUyUGhtAh/l408rAZL05HkpnRIClOBrTQAS4PVyfjhWHD0AibNBa/0hfu27xIL2o9SZXnwcS8Hn4cSPvXQMptP1uHfITMfx8AVfqOE293OXVMz2Jqw5yZLsxepZMu1GlQBjVQBGvG5+e/4l/J093CnJB1sBB1PsdGX/zoEzb1E652d6HqTzruBk9YmlUb1D8LnpbmvgcOL2cbRajPqE+GnszHRT/s0r2GreQeizsqx2IY5wvWuvAmHJayExGOUESRZfoPpYI+uTZ3HVJTqxdYjMLVbKzNkYg6PoKD5XJUu+jyQgTOa8kHTG1OnwmfHwl/HG5W76FqylMOkenn2t/LL4YywZBrEBT8kcEEgfJZNgDAKCElXK8IavactRpxih4ayWC6J3z2VZOVS/kXSDn4GdZj5P/EzbSTBYQbJ3gbEE3BczZTf1t800FaeoGlMjKzq4oG34lPNrnHyV2s+69rk02NeSrO0uEDIpbxuMVQLym9Hkb9wQo76O7rTtvH3y9BRug5N7MuaEVMuDq1RNZE+aDeDuwvlaOTaTgbtXuqmsukWZU/0GGGlL5YWIJEX9tyTM5ezVcE6Irv9K7Nb1LE3SdkdVSYDsdIm7F3QC9DtB/VZYvxbX/wvEXWueRod0FdBVQFcBXQV0FZjGpht3pnQV0FVAVwFdBXQViLvWPI0OPQLySmmtWE8WWQAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" /></p>",
      "OPT4": "<p>\r\n\t<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAF4AAAAoCAYAAAB3qU2yAAAEkUlEQVRoQ+2Zf0yUdRzHX1JrLpHpyLrRVm0FzCxH59iucIs/dIWV8mNiBIwzGP3gtyxZg8MMUZHwSDw04gr6uVDwiJo/MkfMKUVRQdSIZVsrvUwbXcycw6vneTjywcAdd9d9+fHcX8Ceez7f7+v7/nw+78+XOX9LH7SP3wnM0cD7nbkSUAMvhrsGXhD38cE77R/z4uYzJFtSCA0QtbQJ4jr7acyycfumAqJ1N0yxxbm/nP+WmqEuqtfuhPI95OsXuP8mvz3pZKjbwrpiKNuXhT5wqinDPRBXgR+k25yO8XwOx7dEE+TeO/z/lPMnWrNSqQt7ifcKIgn0/wq8jjgGvHOggYSVbTzYYp2iah/drxNH+2aWP+ug7GgFa0KmX8lRgb/IQEMGMTvupL5zE9FBIynsPG0je0UBR4ilSt6k7nc+323iyb0h7FI955kELnHaVsTD+TaIMXPIEovu7EksJRt4Vbft2lnnaMdkyOKbjS00G8OZbgVHBf5nWjNWU0gpx+slAArJc3Q0dHBL/GI6U5OxxTVQE/wp7WFxrPjrV1i6BJ03O3acpLE1iDhDF2krjxJ72ETw4R5CjVFcPBXAvRG6iYHKTTYunrJF5ar1enb8Ir51BfxwN9WRCexeZh5nI65sePsyKbkVlD52m28VpkBM4h3iyNlTxKNulQ6XUL5IpamrAP31IvB5HtNN8DDcbcYQ/yOmzp1SufH1Loekpp5IYl/mJNQ7K8C7LFz8AJn/C/gRN5XYlzoLweNS0G+5HDxgHDs4Sd6+ZstrfPn+t9xa20xZ9E0jOTbUT+v2jRS+1SP9spSk6h0UxYZP0t7Jh2qlvPYYH54IG7dhKwPd+g+47/VKVbaN15M8T31/f/MarkbiOtDF9/NuxlHfxB8Za6E0mbol1VhX/cDez5ZRYviKbX33Uxyr42x7JenG70j8qJ40ady1d+/HUtxG8ISDmIOBjlPMu+s81lcukP7UZV544E3ubjET09NEV1Q2KaFzJVsle/Z1FB6MpEqdbTPH1YxaRzPBiqoDXfZyPqYDFaSFz3VZv04MeUU8nbQKvXpkV5pzCVibyI/4RXEcVSHlikUMGc/5uFxJ1aLn2Vf9BOE3SgqWAX9yD9lbn+Hx1XrJMcl+vY7Gwevoze/lkX/BzygfLyeb55OrMnzl/olJGuMjzrxBwpqvMXo73MglrtJOgpINx1Tgz9FekkRl8NaZMbmO1G0P7mrkcpBXw2C2SSozg1d+Dvfm0kG2sJWciHqOtPmHyDSMgg9Q7mpSaxeyXc6UmXFXM9JiJnc7KWXJLgu9D+VI5cgb0Fe1N6WGr+fdC+q/LyZ7fzkLrUdm4O3kpNq7g/6Gl2m6I53i6BDfDlXqddhtKsX7eoaY1IZ99rAX/4G6hF1xMvX0q5azIK+ZzgI9vsEzjN22geX5ba4IkuJbpOatn473kWPPzAvwPjv8WfkiDbygY9fAa+AFERAUVlO8Bl4QAUFhNcVr4AUREBRWU7wGXhABQWE1xWvgBREQFFZTvAZeEAFBYTXFa+AFERAUVlO8Bl4QAUFhNcULAv8P8Bprp3+pvjAAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" /></p>",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu9": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following sequence of tasks in a preception is correct?<br />\r\n\t<strong>I.</strong> Initialize the weight of the perception randomly.<br />\r\n\t<strong>II.</strong> Go to the next batch of data set.<br />\r\n\t<strong>III.</strong> If the prediction does not match the output, change the weight.<br />\r\n\t<strong>IV.</strong> For a sample input, compute an output.</p>",
      "OPT1": "I, II, III, IV",
      "OPT2": "IV, III, II, I",
      "OPT3": "III, I, II, IV",
      "OPT4": "I, IV, III, I",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu10": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following represents the linkage criteria of hierarchical clustering?</p>",
      "OPT1": "The distance metric used for measuring dissimilarity between clusters.",
      "OPT2": "The method used to initialize cluster centroids.",
      "OPT3": "The number of iterations required for convergence.",
      "OPT4": "The threshold used for merging clusters.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "MfW1aVa49JnBBbjbyREKzA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "MfW1aVa49JnBBbjbyREKzA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu11": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following statements is/are correct?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Manhattan distance captures the distance between two points by aggregating the pairwise absolute difference between each variable.",
      "OPT2": "Manhattan distance captures the distance between two points by aggregating the squared difference in each variable.",
      "OPT3": "Euclidean distance captures the distance between two points of aggregating the squared difference in each variable.",
      "OPT4": "Euclidean distance captures the distance between two points by aggregating the pairwise absolute difference between each variable.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "kANto1cr89QZ3IzSaugRPA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "kANto1cr89QZ3IzSaugRPA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu12": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following statements is/are correct regarding stopping criteria for K-means algorithm?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Convergence is a necessary condition for the stopping criteria in clustering algorithm.",
      "OPT2": "<p>\r\n\tThe variance did not improve by at lease <img align=\"absmiddle\" alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABEAAAARCAYAAAA7bUf6AAABJUlEQVQ4T2P8DwQMFALGwWrIL4ZnG8oZPAo2MDB49jPsmBrAIPHqOMPUmiKG2RLtDEdaHBj4sHgd1TufjjMs3MjHEGhxmiHedQ9DwM5aBuGdlxhUE6wZftxjYtA1kGBgImgITMG/mwwLAyMZljEEMuROL2fwkWLDG/Q4AvYLw7n+MIawq2kMR+YAvUQg9nAY8gFoSDLQkFhyDfnH8OXcXIbWafsYth5TY5h0op7BgQ9bSCCch+SSTwy3D91j4FZ5yzB35jeG5PS/DA1Wixm01vUzeF5axXDaOochRpWB4faCFAbPBgaG2t1zGOJVOcAmIQwBB2YQQ69oJcPqCVEM6lxPGDZmhzMUH9RhyGnLZIjwM2KQYPpBwBAKkv6gTfbk+WnweAcAZRSdzo9AQ4MAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" /></p>\r\n",
      "OPT3": "When the maximum number of iterations has been reached.",
      "OPT4": "None of these",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "1tsLNxDzUM4tAESa/gW9mQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "1tsLNxDzUM4tAESa/gW9mQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu13": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following best describes the role of eigen values in Principal Component Analysis (PCA)?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Eigen values represent the variance captured by each principle component.",
      "OPT2": "Eigen values indicate the correlation between original variable and principal components.",
      "OPT3": "Eigen values are not relevant in PCA.",
      "OPT4": "Eigen values determine the number of principal components to retain.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu14": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following is the primary goal of Principal Component Analysis (PCA)?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Maximize the variance of the original variables.",
      "OPT2": "Transform the original variables into a new set of orthogonal variables.",
      "OPT3": "Preserve all the information from the original data set.",
      "OPT4": "None of these",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu15": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following steps in top-down approach involves adjusting model parameters to optimize performance?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Feature selection",
      "OPT2": "Model evaluation",
      "OPT3": "Hyperparameter tuning",
      "OPT4": "Data preprocessing",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu16": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tGiven an input layer with three nodes <img align=\"absmiddle\" alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAFkAAAAYCAYAAACRD1FmAAAFiUlEQVRoQ+2Xe0yVdRjHPzhXGznLvJ0stT84Mk3TWE68IZOjizJu5oVSwUBIQOSywpYIihZIwAFBhTBFT5I4EFS8dSRwpDjsZDh0SumsRszVMHZG6PDQ79y4KXJuuFbn/fN939/z/N7P+32+z/Nz6BAX9mtACTjYIQ8oX11wO+SBZ2yH/AQY2yHbIT8JAiKHpknFiVMlFDT7URjtwmAb5/2fe7IaVcZSlmZe02F9bn0xNXbINpaYIVy7KgNXvyywQx4YwNqoesj5jE0soTjQmUE2TuXQ8eB2R1n4MmJPwkL5IbJ9JNyp/ZJNAYWM3llMkvsIK1Pep7E0jjeiSsEzg1M5PkjuXCBnYwxfSD6jeqs7Q63MYO1yPeQDuMiPkufz0uPDaX7BXF4Of1V91XF0tIwZF2LwPCKjPEfCmW/HErAAbiFlquQp676h5QIFZUPxda0VMZX4nI5n+Ok6pIGzabs5iCnTJCYqp4WGyhL2p6RSeK1V7OlV/JM2Ev7edCRa6WmaUJWf4MjOyzjFzeWnlET9e44yInZ8RLCHlCGGL9E2umOFu4jPVNKKBDfZy1xSXse1X8gaWs59jbm8OhufpmEfixfshYA4chLeZIyta0ZznQJffw7iy7pdcSwaY97Pa1ftYFXdQhS6cr4rGlaQaFh/E1FSRNQYJSGu0VToIEqYH5POloiZjLpzli2rI1Hcfof8mgTcRcmoVTks81MK1W4nzscZx6ZaDmZvJVHxK/P7hdylN3N4dU0X7Srk04O5mmBCyVikbUMnrw+hOl9YhtkxNKgbqjlb/zu3jsvJVjaJCMO6gfmDyo2LCVZMJa0mHW+JdhAzTg9O+nujfhY/2o8kPuTkkUCkBiGZZRfGfZvBqwuyuhb5kkiuhh7u35fMBqRdYFBf/UoLIBt9/QxjV8QSIpsrVHkcjx4+2gvooyA7VhPvupqTa3qOahZBNoOXAbIAkJXM7h+qqHmxVzPq9LorvL431aAQcykLFar2sG1nBeXnJ5ClK12dkQp1HiUl8hO9f05cRVpWLN7SXq1QZzU9FfgwGBMgj6gT1bqY7HEJViq5L173adINDSlUtDrivGIb8g1eOFR9f7vDqaWYvLvehCDHLVdK0d55XNl1jVmhz1J+qA23effY7fcdb3WWobbPaL0smcLhGzgUPb2zqfTEL5rVuZs84/Qne3JbCQp9QOKsA0wqycCzroja2WuYUbOfqx6h4ueJct+8luDLvj0A6OIZId//gKLD4UxTX9RNJ5nKeybaxfPEf5NPgLTN4OWN3XxbP+lkKluY0t8Ip27g3I2n6ZNX/DTOrytlfEI0bpoTRMjymKAowsFnvGvHyMR80gNfwbGxVDyIpnpWJElh/rztYuj8TaWisVR0g9xGw75gPLePJE2ZgndfTcwAJ23kxxyWv4uz42/68adqMhGfrmW5l4t+MjBcOnUGQV5tNC49zrZCIZWpBAXmc93Q2DbNrMFnSZYwIXFSk8mYpFRyvjOS0auhLNiLWGVzl397DeZSdjzvp2snC6G2gCxyF9V1xmJYJEUP5dcH1je7XPrk5XSDnLLRhK+U0ioqN6V6MuGiAZt2rO4NWQcvhIurD4i5epyJI1h/FqP9cWuJag57TGX0F+Nf8NxYdT/qx8f1BUmWQNaIw8UWtt71Z7tQv3H2tPbzNKKKopPUhKUKxQ+x9fxo7e4sWK9p7LQ/y5RsQc7HLhGdekdyAws3LP9vANabCy2Vm5mjeM00Jeu9SEVgt8ZnM87qegqSzzA+Ihx3a0+XNtuUZYE0DQoiFC+wKcEDSav4rqjPaQ7L6A9yO02lMcyJOmbI2n34t2wjPVYZS6qgrtvtifpTnIutjMgG+zQ1RC8/Nh7nTbMLU5PY33skATvkJyCMfwADJhPIdGh0cQAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" /> having value 0.7, 0.5 and 0.3 respectively, associated with weights 0.2, 0.3 and \u20130.2. If the bias is 0.48 and a binary sigmoid activation function is used, find the output of the neural network? (Rounded upto 2 decimal)</p>",
      "OPT1": "0.67 [0.66 - 0.68]",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "l7TOLEy9fjwAhzRCspf47fqNNj/FIJd/ilBAGOu9jjQ=",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu17": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tHow does a feedforward neural network differ from other types of neural networks?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Feedforward neural networks allow feedback connections between neurons.",
      "OPT2": "Feedforward neural networks can only have one layer of neurons.",
      "OPT3": "Feedforward neural networks do not contain any hidden layers.",
      "OPT4": "In feedforward neural networks, information flows in one direction, from input to output, without cycles or loops.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "TEST_NAME": "Discovered Test 6464881",
  "TEST_ID_ENCODED": "NjQ2NDg4MQ==",
  "TEST_ID": "NjQ2NDg4MQ=="
}